https://www.swinog.ch/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.swinog.ch.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you fill in contact forms we save this data to be able to get back to you.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We might include some google analytics tracker.
Who we share your data with
No one. Period.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
How we protect your data
We will store the password-hash encrypted in a database. All the other information are stored plain-text.
SwiNOG #37 – May 4th 2021 SwiNOG #36 is over – Presentations are published!
Please mark in your calendar:
SwiNOG #37 will be held in Berne on May 4th 2021. (Unfortunately due to  COVID-19 we’ll have no SwiNOG in 2020)
Latest news
SwiNOG #36 – Registration is open
September 15, 2019
SwiNOG #36 – Call for Papers & Sponsors (2019-Nov-14)
July 30, 2019
SwiNOG #35 – Registration is open
March 5, 2019
SwiNOG #35 – Call for Papers
February 12, 2019
SwiNOG #34 – first videos published
December 14, 2018
Twitter @swinog
RT @GovCERT_CH: Huge Lokibot malspam wave ongoing targeting German speaking Internet users, pretending that the attachment has been scanned… - 2 weeks agoSwiNOG #37 posponed due to COVID-19
https://t.co/iE25CMDX52 - 9 months agoRT @mrmouse79: #coronavirus #COVID19 any (positive) impact on #IPv6? #AskingForAFriend - 9 months ago_cat getTextFromPDF(fetch('https://t.co/WUa1xjE4GC')) | grep "s/Foundation(.*)\n/$1/"_
The community SwiNOG exists… https://t.co/zzAMcNYL3A - 10 months agoMerry Christmas to all of you. See you next year! https://t.co/yWT3DCSXQo - 12 months ago658 followersVisit @swinog's Profile
Facebook ***SwiNOG 37 postponed due to COVID.19***Dear CommunityAfter careful consideration of risks and benefits and with a heavy heart, we have decided not to go forward with SwiNOG #37 in May 2020 due to the highly uncertain situation regarding the SARS-CoV-2 virus. The critical factors are the travelling, the restrictions placed on events by the government and first and foremost our concern for the health and safety of all our attendees and speakers.We are currently talking to our sponsors and partners to find a solution on how to proceed. We are very sorry we can't give you the great conference in May that many of you have been eagerly anticipating. We do hope you understand that this was, in every way, a very tough decision for us to make. We are trying to do the right thing by putting the health of all of us first.Instead of the two meetings in May and November, we plan for one big Event on Tuesday, September 8th, 2020.If you have any question do not hesitate to contact us.The SwiNOG Core Team ... See MoreSee Less 9 months ago  ·  View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by Email_cat getTextFromPDF(fetch('https://swinog.ch/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/2019_SwiNOG_Prospect_Sponsoring_en.pdf')) | grep "s/Foundation(.*)\n/$1/"_The community SwiNOG exists since February 24, 2000***HAPPY BIRTHDAY!*** ... See MoreSee Lessswinog.chl.facebook.com
10 months ago  ·  View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailWhich future for instant messaging in the SwiNOG community? Telegram, Matrix, good old IRC or something else? Here's my take: swinot.ch/post-irc/ ... See MoreSee Lessswinot.chl.facebook.com
10 months ago  ·  View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by Email
Copyright © by SwiNOG Organisation
Follow us:
Privacy Policy | Contact us
Scroll to Top
